What is she playing?
The Butterfly Lovers.
Such a classic.
Liang Xiaoyu is playing the piano.
(Zhao Xilun and Sun Qimeng
return to the Signal House)
Thanks.
No problem.
Hello.
Hi.
Hi, babe.
You two are wearing
such matching colors today.
Thanks.
Did you have fun?
Yeah.
It was pretty fun.
I'll put my stuff down first.
You look handsome today too.
Thanks.
You look pretty too.
I need to go upstairs.
I'll head up for a bit.
Meng, I'll head upstairs first.
Okay.
Meng, shall we
take some photos together later?
Sure.
Hello.
I brought my dog out today.
I just got out of bed.
I took a nap earlier.
So you didn't go out today?
No, I didn't.
He doesn't know.
Today, Meng and I
went to...
We went to a park.
And I brought my dog along.
It was pretty fun.
Have you eaten?
Yeah. I cooked for myself.
(Looks toward the door)
(Gets up) He can hear everything.
He's right outside the door.
He can hear us, right?
Yeah.
Maybe we should go outside.
No.
It's just that I have
mixed feelings.
I'm feeling a little dizzy now.
I'm just a little tired.
He's here.
Chen Hewen...
He hasn't seen this many people before.
(Stops)
(Looks)
Oh my god.
He left?
(Looks down)
She's disappointed.
How about...
Why did he go back to his spot again?
I was going to ask you
to go rock climbing.
But,
I saw Yu Yang and Fang over there.
My secret spot
has been discovered.
Is he writing in his diary?
Could he possibly be
writing someone a note or something?
What did he write?
I apologize for the things I've done
without considering your feelings.
But,
have you considered my feelings?
I think
Chen Hewen is upset too.
He's been keeping it
bottled up.
What's wrong
with giving in a little
in a relationship?
Yeah.
They're still angry.
A small misunderstanding
turns into a big one.
I originally wanted
to bring some food back.
But today, I really
spent the whole time driving,
so I didn't get a chance
to buy any food.
(Eye mask from Zhao Xilun)
(Checking out)
(Puts it down)
This is a photo of the two of them.
She put it down.
She picked it up again.
It still hurts a little.
Liang Xiaoyu...
What happened?
How did something suddenly appear here?
What?
This one.
I brought this back.
I didn't even notice it.
It suddenly appeared after I
came back from the bathroom.
Yeah, I conjured it up.
I just
- came back,
- I conjured it up.
and you called me.
Then, this thing suddenly appeared.
That's amazing.
What did you guys do today?
We played tennis today.
And what food did you have?
We had
Western food.
Western food?
Steak and shrimp.
So much happened to me today.
After thinking it over,
I told him
that we should just be friends.
(Opens arms)
Yes, Liang Xiaoyu.
You're amazing.
I just feel like he's been
avoiding me, and I don't
seem to be getting any response
from him.
So I decided to let it go.
I feel like I'm pressuring him
by taking the initiative.
So I thought I might as well let it go.
Yesterday,
I really overthought everything.
Why did you think so much?
I felt
really upset
after the event ended.
Yeah.
I feel like always being
the one to take the initiative
isn't that great.
No,
I don't think
there's anything wrong with that.
Then I thought about it for a long time.
I figured everything out on the rooftop.
Luckily, we had this date.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have known
how to tell him.
Geez.
Yeah.
(Moves closer)
Many things
are flashing
through my mind now.
Like what?
I don't know
how I'm supposed
to stay here anymore.
Everyone is paired up.
(Reaches out)
You...
You have me.
I'll be with you.
Female friendships are truly wonderful.
If anyone asks,
(Cui Yihang and Sun Bohan
return to the Signal House)
shall we tell them about this?
Don't say anything.
I think so too.
Just say something unexpected came up.
That's really nice.
So nice of them.
Hi, guys.
Hello.
They went to fly kites.
They went kite-flying.
What about the other two?
Well,
something came up.
The fact that they revealed nothing
really gets me.
I really like that.
Very gentlemanly.
I think that's very mature.
Hello.
Did you come back together?
They don't want
to ruin everyone else's mood either.
You guys...
We'll head upstairs first.
You guys go ahead.
They're finally back.
Who?
Probably
our roommates.
Are they here?
Are they?
They're back.
Where?
Downstairs.
Hey.
So pretty.
You guys look amazing today.
You guys went together?
Were all four of you together today?
In pairs.
No.
Something came up for them.
Yeah.
Seriously?
I'm heading back.
They're okay, right?
Nothing...
nothing serious, right?
Something came up.
They might have to...
I don't know.
Nothing else. Yeah.
It's nothing serious.
I'm heading back.
Go ahead.
But they look really down.
A little.
Sun Bohan and Cui Yihang seem
kind of down.
Just open the curtains.
Yeah.
Looking at photos.
He's worried sick.
(City date invitation card from Xing)
The invitation card.
What's up, Sun Bohan?
That smile...
Looks like he's smiling through tears.
How was your day?
Where'd you go?
We went to a dog park today.
I brought my dog along.
Did you guys...
You...
You didn't go?
No, something came up.
They...
Yeah, uh...
Something with Xing.
She's okay, right?
She's fine.
So where'd you guys go?
What?
He couldn't hold it in.
Oh my God.
He tried, but he couldn't.
You...
What's wrong?
What happened?
It's okay.
I don't know what happened.
But if you...
If you don't wanna talk, don't.
Um...
It's okay.
Take a minute to calm down.
Need more tissues?
No, I'm fine.
I'm okay now.
Okay, take some time to process it.
I can't.
Seeing him hurts now.
- What do I do?
- I get you.
Let's ask Sun Bohan what's going on.
Look at him.
What's he doing?
What's he up to?
Chen Hewen's eavesdropping.
- Can't you see him?
- Look at Chen Hewen's pose.
Hello? Anyone there?
Who is it?
It's Chen Hewen.
I'm right here.
He's "trapped himself" in there.
Where are you?
Right here.
Hello.
Then I'll...
He's crazy!
I'm leaving.
Come here.
This is hilarious.
You're seriously crazy.
It's like you're running
a little store here.
Hello,
what can I get you?
Let's go find Sun Bohan first.
We'll come buy something later.
Then the store is closed for now.
Oh my God.
He's so funny.
Sun Bohan.
What's up?
We wanted to ask what happened to Xing.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
Why didn't Xing and Si come back?
Something came up.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing, really.
We were just...
What was it?
We talked for a bit.
Sun Bohan's a real one.
He won't spill a thing.
Okay.
Thanks for checking on us.
We'll just...
You know...
Rest for a bit.
It's fine. Really.
Then I...
I'll...
I'll head out first.
Okay, you guys go ahead.
Don't look at me.
Just now...
Liang Xiaoyu and Meng
knocked on our door.
They asked what happened to Xing.
Can we talk about it?
It's nothing.
It's just
something personal.
Something unexpected happened.
You'll find out later.
You'll know.
Sun Bohan's really hurting.
Right now, he won't
think about anything else.
He'll only think,
I didn't take
good care of Xing.
Yeah.
If I'd told her before,
"You need to eat on time, "
or if I'd looked after her,
this wouldn't have
happened.
He'll blame it all on
not taking good care of her.
And
when she was pushing through it,
maybe he didn't even notice.
Right.
On the city date,
she even came over
and asked him out
- herself.
- Yeah.
Sun Bohan must
feel like
he failed her somehow.
(Sun Bohan consumed by guilt)
So he'll just sink deeper
into those feelings.
Self-blame.
Guilt.
I think Yue'er
will probably have
a little talk with Chen Hewen.
But so far,
we haven't seen it.
What Chen Hewen wrote down
shows that he finally
got those feelings
off his chest.
He has feelings too.
(Sha Yue'er and Chen Hewen
both emotional)
Zhao Xilun opened up,
(Zhao Xilun and Sun Qimeng talk openly)
and he and Meng
had a brief goodbye.
As for Liang Xiaoyu and Chen Hewen,
she feels pretty good
(Xiaoyu and Hewen grow closer)
when they're together.
They're growing closer.
And that's
everything
from the first day of dates.
Throughout the day,
we
got to see
so many different feelings and emotions.
Now, on day two,
it's time for more dates.
Let's see
how they'll go.
Alright, let's watch.
Hi.
Can we get our hair washed?
Sure. Right this way.
Okay.
Thanks.
I'm seriously gonna fall asleep.
Let's start washing your hair.
Mm-hmm.
How've you been?
Pretty good.
You've got a date today, right?
Yeah.
Hi,
these are the hair products
you'll be using today.
Pantene's new 3-Minute Gold Series.
What a coincidence.
I've been using this too.
The gold formula really sparkles.
Even hair care can feel this fancy.
Of course.
It contains
10x concentrated Pro-V B5 essence.
It repairs dry, frizzy hair
and nourishes it from within.
Your hair won't just feel smooth.
It'll shine too.
No wonder your hair's
been so shiny lately.
Let's go dry your hair.
Okay.
So smooth and shiny.
It's like a built-in glow.
And it has a luxurious neroli scent.
Seriously.
Perfect for date vibes.
Now you're glowing all over.
You're ready for a perfect pic anytime.
Mm-hmm.
(Jasmine flowers he prepared)
Jasmine.
Yue'er.
Outdoor hiking?
They're going hiking.
Zhao Xilun looks excited.
Nervous.
He's getting shy.
Hello.
Flowers.
These
are your favorite jasmine flowers.
Thank you.
Happy.
Here, hold them.
(Hands her the flowers with both hands)
Thank you.
They look better with you holding them.
They smell so good.
Thank you.
After you.
Thanks.
Hello, you two.
Welcome to Baqi Cave Adventure Park.
Today, you'll be trying
our via ferrata.
Our professional instructors
will help you gear up.
Okay.
Alright, come on.
Hold this for me.
Via ferrata.
(Slime, via ferrata)
Last time was so safe.
Now we're doing something this intense.
You're full of surprises.
I just wanted to try something
more adventurous with you.
I've actually done
this once.
It was along a cliff.
You clip in and make your way around.
When two people
are both nervous,
it makes those feelings even stronger.
This bandana's pretty hip-hop.
(Zhao "Hip-Hop" Lun)
We have to wear bandanas too?
Pirate.
This look actually suits you.
Slow down.
Okay.
Take it slow.
You too.
Okay.
You're not nervous, right?
I am.
Good. You should be.
(Joking)
They both look pretty happy.
They're relaxed.
Duck a little.
Careful. Don't hit your head.
What?
(Under professional supervision.
Do not imitate.)
This is indoors.
It's this high?
(Via ferrata starting point)
This is our starting point.
We'll go around once,
then take the zip line.
(High-altitude bungee jump)
This?
This is terrifying.
Zhao Xilun, I "hate" you.
(Swaying)
Why is it swaying?
If I get too scared halfway through,
can I get down?
Once you start, there's no turning back.
Just like us.
(No turning back)
Well played.
He pulled the "bungee effect" on her.
You okay?
I'll steady you.
Look at that little glance.
I'll give it a try.
I think you can do it.
We can do this.
Let's go.
(Takes the first step)
So brave.
You can do it. I'm coming.
(Quickly moves closer and waits)
You okay?
I feel so much safer with you behind me.
(I feel so much safer
with you behind me)
Crouch down a little.
(Supports her)
You're okay.
(Steadies her)
Go ahead.
I'll help you.
It's okay. I'll catch you.
(It's okay. I'll catch you)
Okay, Zhao Xilun.
I'm coming over!
(Reaches out)
Pull me!
(Grabs her hand)
See? Pretty steady, right?
We're so good at this.
Careful.
Watch your step.
Okay.
You okay?
(Keeps checking on her)
Yeah.
Careful. It's really slippery here.
(Keeps reminding her)
(Matches her pace)
Hold on.
(Steadies her)
We did it again.
I'm counting on you,
math whiz.
Now you're suddenly being sweet.
Aren't I always sweet?
You've already been really brave.
I'm one of The Courageous now too.
(I'm one of The Courageous now too)
Yeah.
You're one of The Courageous too.
We finally made it to the end.
(Finish: Rappelling platform)
We're at the rappelling platform.
(Under professional supervision.
Do not imitate.)
You two did amazing.
You made it all the way here.
Seriously impressive.
Thank you, coach.
I think we did pretty great too.
We can do this.
Come on, let's get ready.
(Ready to go)
Take it slow.
Just one step.
Just this one.
Here, watch out.
Don't scrape against this.
You got this.
(Zhao Xilun)
I think you can do it.
This is kinda scary.
It's kinda high.
This is terrifying.
Hold on with both hands.
(Takes a deep breath)
You got this.
Anything you want to say to each other?
Say it loud.
I hope we'll both be braver from now on.
(Under professional supervision.
Do not imitate.)
We got this!
We really can do this!
Double meaning.
Okay.
Okay?
You got this, Zhao Xilun.
Cheering each other on.
(Under professional supervision.
Do not imitate.)
(Watches closely)
We got this!
Oh my God.
(Waves)
It's totally safe!
It's totally safe?
I'm completely fine.
(Sha Yue'er)
You can do it, Sha Yue'er!
I'll catch you.
Okay!
That's what he
most wanted to tell her.
But it still
didn't cross the line.
Right.
But deep down, that's
what he wanted to say.
He's like, let's both be a little braver.
Let's both be a little braver,
right?
We can definitely do this.
I'll catch you.
Let's both be a little braver.
Zhao Xilun,
(Sha Yue'er)
I don't know what to say either.
I want to be brave too!
(I want to be brave too)
You will!
You got this!
(You will. You got this)
You definitely can.
(Under professional supervision.
Do not imitate.)
Don't be scared. I'm here!
This...
See? Not too bad, right?
(Steadies her)
Not too bad, right?
That was terrifying!
You did great.
(Hold onto each other)
You were really brave.
That was great. We were so brave.
Feels pretty good now that
it's over, right?
Yeah!
(Claps in celebration)
We did amazing.
But if you're tired,
we can go eat.
Let's eat.
Then let's go eat.
Let's go.
What if I want to hear you sing?
I didn't know a car ride
came with a concert.
What do you want to hear?
Wanting Freedom.
(Teasing)
Okay.
How does it go again?
It won't sound bad.
♪For the future♪
Make your voice higher.
(Higher voice)
♪For the future♪
(Even higher)
♪Hard♪
Why are you laughing at yourself?
They're happy.
Oh my God.
Did you have fun today?
So much fun.
We're almost there.
Let's change first.
Ladies first, okay?
Thank you.
Such a gentleman.
So pretty.
Wow.
Sit.
Okay.
Wow.
This feels so nice.
Have a sip.
My mouth's kinda dry.
Here.
Thanks.
How'd you know
I wanted this one?
You always drink this one.
(You always drink this one)
That's so thoughtful.
(So thoughtful)
Cheers.
Let's dig in.
Let's eat.
You look really good in white.
Not many people can pull off white.
Zhao Xilun really suits white.
But not many can pull off pink either.
You look great in pink too.
You just have to be really fair.
Then it looks good on you.
You're really fair too.
Not as fair as you.
See?
Oh my gosh.
Had to respond.
Wait here a sec.
I'm gonna use the restroom.
What's going on?
Okay.
Was that
a little random?
Yeah.
Just a sec.
I knew it.
So thoughtful.
This is for you.
Thanks.
Wanna guess first?
What it is?
It's not food, is it?
I brought you some snacks.
Seriously?
Can I open it?
Sure.
Okay, can I sit down?
You can.
Sit.
So...
So what do you think it is?
It's not a cake, is it?
Take a guess.
What could it be?
You wouldn't hold a cake like that.
(Watching closely)
It's not food.
Black tea?
(A custom-named perfume, Yilun Mingyue)
Yilun Mingyue.
Oh my gosh!
That name...
That's clever.
(A name with a special meaning)
This is their scent.
What do you think of Yilun Mingyue?
Haitao, think they'll work out?
Stay tuned.
Wow.
I remember
you said you liked tea scents.
And I remembered
you said you liked perfume.
So I went and bought it.
Do you wear perfume a lot?
Yeah, I do.
What scents do you like?
I'm into tea scents right now.
Tea scents.
(Remembered)
Zhao Xilun's pretty thoughtful too.
Yeah.
I bought this on June 6.
The date just felt lucky.
Six-six.
I love this scent.
She really does like it.
Yeah.
So thoughtful.
(Yilun Mingyue)
Nice.
Yilun Mingyue.
Don't read it out loud.
Even he gets shy.
Just say you saw it.
Don't read it out loud.
It's like when someone posts online,
and you read their caption out loud.
That's kinda cute.
(Blushing)
Suddenly...
He's blushing.
It's just a little something.
I really wanted to thank you for today.
You were really brave today.
Otherwise, I probably
wouldn't have done any of that.
I think you were brave too.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have dared go up there alone.
(If it weren't for you, I wouldn't
have dared go up there alone)
He's blushing.
The Courageous.
Blushing again.
What about your future career?
Any plans right now?
Now they're talking about future plans.
I'm still figuring it out.
But I think I'm still
pretty career-driven.
I don't really want
to drift through life doing nothing.
Of course.
You gotta try different things.
I wanna figure it out before I'm 25.
That's how I see it.
I had a lot
of
idealized views of certain industries.
But after interning,
those slowly started fading.
I get it.
But right now, I'm definitely
a lot more certain than before.
If you can do it,
it means you understand enough.
If you can't, you don't
understand enough yet.
That's so well said.
Unity of knowledge and action.
(Unity of knowledge and action)
That's Wang Yangming.
They're on the same wavelength.
Learn by doing.
Just like you said.
Like that unity of knowledge and action.
Just do things first,
then see how you feel.
Exactly.
I slowly learn through practice,
by actually doing things myself.
You're pretty practical too.
Yeah, I was gonna say
he's really practical.
He really puts knowledge into action.
Zhao Xilun
knows what he wants,
and he goes for it.
Why did you choose math?
(Curious)
When I chose math,
besides genuinely liking it,
I also thought it was really practical
as a major.
I totally get that.
One thing I like about math
is that its answers
are pretty definite.
At least, that's how I see it.
With the basic math I've studied.
No.
I've only studied basic math too.
We're just
casually chatting
about advanced math.
Yeah.
I think everyone
has their own view of a subject.
I like math because
there's a beauty to its logic.
(Beauty of logic)
Am I not allowed to be serious?
What?
I sound like I'm interviewing you.
Well, I like...
Why did I choose math?
Once you really get into it,
you realize it's actually a language.
A beautiful language.
And it's
universal.
Say aliens came
to Earth right now.
Their math would still work like ours.
Because it's based on logic.
As long as logic exists,
math exists.
That means you're really logical.
Looking at Zhao Xilun now,
I get this feeling.
He's really like
a grown-up Little Prince.
Yeah.
Right?
It's an abstract idea,
so it's always years ahead
of the real world.
It's almost like it quietly points us
toward where humanity's headed.
Oh my gosh.
Like, you invent a mathematical tool,
and then years later,
people use it.
It just feels kind of magical.
Bonus points.
Then why didn't you keep studying math
and become a mathematician?
Well...
Math takes a lot of natural talent.
It's like if I were
only 1.6 meters tall.
I'd never make it in pro basketball.
I get it.
That's what I mean.
But when it comes to math,
you're definitely taller than 1.6 meters.
That's some high praise.
Happy.
No, maybe I really am just 1.6 meters.
You're too modest.
Oh my gosh.
His face is red.
Totally red.
I think you're really talented.
Talking to you,
you just seem really smart.
Come on. How am I smart?
(Asks)
Tell me more.
Why do you have to think about it?
Asking that already proves you're smart.
You instantly threw me
into a brief panic.
(Cracks up)
Because when I talk to you,
I can tell
you really think for yourself.
And you have your own goals.
Even though we're probably both
in a pretty...
(In unison)
Uncertain stage.
See? You're smart.
You knew what I was gonna say.
You always know your general direction
and what keeps you moving forward.
When we talked on the first day,
you said you were afraid
of being abandoned.
My parents both moved abroad back then.
It was my first time living at school.
Everything just
happened around that time.
So I think I developed this deep...
feeling of being abandoned.
I do think
a lot of things from childhood
can really affect you.
But I think you...
At least from what you show
on the outside,
you don't come across that way.
It's like you've
wrapped yourself in layers of armor.
Kind of.
Deep down, is it just
really hard for you to truly trust...
someone?
You really get me.
(You really get me)
You know, actually,
coming to the Signal House
has been really
surreal for me.
The Signal House is really close
to my ninth-grade school.
I used to walk this road every day,
and I'd always feel so down.
I had so many ideas,
and so much potential
I thought I had,
but never lived up to.
Back then, I thought,
I was like,
I'll probably never walk
this road again.
Back in middle school,
I never would've imagined
that years later...
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd come back
in this
kind of way
and walk this road again.
What a coincidence.
But since coming to the Signal House,
I've kept receiving
kindness and encouragement
from everyone.
So what's been
one of the happiest times in your life?
Every year has its own happiness.
So overall,
your life's been pretty happy?
Not really.
It's been bittersweet.
(Bittersweet)
Longing for happiness
But bittersweet still means there's joy.
(But bittersweet still means
there's joy)
It's like taking a glass
of water and adding
one drop of red paint.
No matter how few drops, it turns red.
And red is joy.
This guy, seriously.
I'm telling you,
LunYue Full Moon
is already hanging in the air.
Right?
Okay.
He's all positive vibes.
If there's joy,
and every year has some,
then I'd call that a happy life.
(If every year has joy,
that's happiness)
Yeah, that's pretty good.
Yeah.
I'm still kinda hungry. What do I do?
Didn't expect that one, did you?
That's some serious "food chemistry".
"Food chemistry"?
"Food chemistry".
I always thought I made food look good.
Then I saw you eating that time,
and I realized
you make food look good too.
I feel like such a goofball.
Oh no.
Don't your friends
describe you that way?
Only my really close friends do.
People who don't
know me well say I'm aloof.
I don't think you're aloof.
Sometimes I think you're really smart.
Because sometimes my brain
works in really weird ways,
but you always keep up.
You always keep up.
(You always get how my brain works)
His face is seriously red.
It's been red this whole time.
You're full?
Haven't I been, you know...
Dieting?
You get puffy that easily?
I retain water easily.
My eyes can get so swollen
I can barely open them sometimes.
That's pretty swollen.
Do you get puffy easily?
Not really.
But if I cry the night before,
I'll be really puffy the next day.
So, have you cried here
at the Signal House?
(Freezes)
Both times she cried
had something to do with Chen Hewen.
Can I ask about that?
Don't.
That's in the past.
I didn't expect that.
Didn't expect that.
I'm the type who's
calm on the outside,
but a storm inside.
I remember telling you that.
So is there a storm inside right now?
Right now, this very second?
Kinda.
That "kinda"
isn't literally just "kinda".
It's probably
a little more than that.
There's definitely
a storm inside me now.
Ever since you said you
were still hungry,
I've been all stirred up.
Here.
Thanks.
At the Signal House,
what's been your happiest
moment or day so far?
(Fidgets)
Definitely getting this.
(Definitely getting this)
LunYue
Full Moon.
(LunYue Full Moon)
Didn't see that coming, huh?
Me suddenly saying, "I'm still hungry."
Yeah, I feel like
so many conversations just suddenly stop
with, "I'm still hungry".
Don't you think I'm really genuine?
I do.
I really like that about you.
You're just agreeing with me.
Always saying what I wanna hear.
How am I doing that?
With the things you say.
You say what I like hearing.
Then I'll change.
No need.
I kinda like it.
I should still be myself.
Just be genuine.
I will.
I like genuine people.
(I like genuine people)
Now you're saying
what I want to hear.
They're going back and forth!
Full circle.
Those math lessons paid off.
- Yeah.
- That logic
just keeps stacking up.
It all connects.
Smart.
You struck a chord with me.
What?
Nothing.
That earned him points.
I think she's starting
to see him differently.
She's reassessing him.
Yeah.
He's slowly getting into her heart.
Things are different now.
(Eye contact)
That mysterious smile again.
We've never seen that look from her.
What? Is my hair messed up?
You look good.
You look good too,
but I have to watch the road.
(You look good, but eyes on the road)
I know.
(Keep it coming!)
- This is too sweet!
- Oh my God!
Oh my God!
He just scored big.
What else?
I think LunYue Full Moon
could actually work.
I can see it.
The vibe is perfect.
He's really funny.
Humor is so important in a guy.
Yeah.
She can't stop smiling.
What now?
Here's his chance, guys.
And every time
Zhao Xilun shows up,
it's always...
Maybe it's fate.
It's not that he
always shows up
at the perfect time.
He never left.
(Can't hold it in)
That's true.
Even last time when they were
in the ball pit,
I said it then.
Zhao Xilun is a strong contender,
but he takes things slowly.
And with Sha Yue'er,
he's the type
who slowly, layer by layer,
(Step by step)
opens up your heart.
And he's like,
it's okay if you don't notice me.
I'll stay by your side
until you finally do.
And he doesn't pry.
Like, when Sha Yue'er cried,
he got the hint and stopped.
He just focuses on
what's between him and Sha Yue'er.
- I only care about
- Yeah.
the time we spend together.
I stay focused on that.
(Just enjoy the moment)
Just be happy.
When you meet someone
who's on your wavelength
and really gets you,
you can just be totally at ease.
No more overthinking.
It feels so much easier.
They're creating
new experiences
for each other
together.
Sha Yue'er herself
gets scared
when things move too fast.
But Zhao Xilun gives her something
slow and steady.
And at the same time,
he'll stay right by her side.
I think at her age,
because she's so young,
she doesn't really know
which person
is someone
she thinks she likes,
and who's someone
who always
makes things feel fresh
and makes her happy.
Once she experiences both, she'll know
what she
actually wants.
Chen Hewen needs a plan.
Seriously.
If all he can do is write
those few words,
that's not gonna cut it.
Right now,
he won't even leave the house.
He's inside playing shopkeeper.
Those two barely
got any sweetness.
It's been all struggle.
No idea why.
Alright, everyone.
Our second date may
bring us some
surprises and shocks.
And we'll also send
our heartfelt wishes
to Xing.
Up next,
what kind of sweet date
will Cao Yiheng and Cui Kaiyi
bring us this time?
(Smiles)
They're both wearing matching colors.
(Walks quickly)
Flowers again?
They're my favorite pair to watch.
Pure sweetness.
They feel so bright and cheerful.
Yeah.
(Takes her bag)
I'll carry it.
So pretty.
Flowers every day.
They match our outfits.
Yeah.
(They match our outfits)
(Shipping them)
(A handmade jewelry studio)
They're making something.
Do you know what we're doing today?
Are we making bracelets?
Yeah, crafts.
(Pulls out her chair)
Give it to me.
I got you a gift.
Yeah.
I'll hold the flowers.
Is this for me?
Yeah.
(Exchange gifts)
Put it here.
Look, they both brought gifts.
They're meeting each other halfway.
Let's see the gifts.
(Smiles)
Let me see.
(Opens the gift)
(Watches)
He can't wait
to see her reaction.
It's a camera?
(Smiles)
(Surprised)
An instant camera.
You read my mind.
How'd you know I wanted one?
Wasn't it obvious?
That went straight to her heart.
This one's so pretty.
(Listens closely)
Instant cameras are getting really good.
Now I really want to buy one.
(Hears it)
(Instant camera)
Your wishing fountain
is right beside you.
Exactly.
No Master Kong Jasmine Coins needed.
Your wish just comes true.
Remembering the little things
she says really matters.
Yeah.
I'm taking pictures every day now.
A fragrance, right?
Aromatherapy.
(Sleep aromatherapy)
Yeah.
(Surprised)
Didn't you say
you don't sleep very well?
It's for sleep.
(Glances)
I used to have terrible insomnia.
(Sleep aromatherapy)
They both remember the little things.
I never would've guessed.
Do you like it?
Yes if it's from you.
(I like anything you give me)
Oh my gosh.
I'll fall asleep
to this every night now.
(It's more than aromatherapy.
It's company every night)
So you'll think of me, right?
She's smooth.
You'll think of me, right?
Yeah.
How do we make these?
There are so many.
They're so pretty.
They really look like fruit.
Can we just pick any?
Yeah.
(Thinking)
I'll make yours, and you make mine.
(Make bracelets for each other)
Absolutely.
(Smiles)
She's so happy.
I'm wearing it every day.
(Thinking hard)
For mine...
(Cao Yiheng)
You can make
my bracelet
in your style.
Yeah. Let's start.
Yeah.
Pick whatever you want.
We can make different styles.
We can make a few.
Yeah.
(Smells it)
Which one do you like? Let me guess.
This is the one
you couldn't smell earlier.
(Gets a tissue)
Thanks.
No problem.
It's okay.
(Takes off his jacket)
You were sweating earlier.
With the AC blowing on you now,
(Worried she'll catch a cold)
it might get worse.
Okay, I'll listen to you.
(Puts it on)
She's putting it on.
It's still warm from him.
But this is gonna ruin
my outfit today.
It won't.
(Rolls up sleeves)
Fine, I'll wear it.
It's the same color palette.
Yeah.
Cui Kaiyi.
So cute.
I'm starting to get the hang of this.
When it comes to aesthetics,
(Compliments him)
you're still the expert.
You're getting better too.
(Compliment each other)
I match things to my mood.
Looks like you're in a good mood.
It's all thanks to you.
(It's all thanks to you)
Let me get your approval first.
I don't need to check it.
I think it's great.
Yours is so pretty.
That's a muralist's eye.
Let me tweak yours.
Anything you make looks good.
When you start grad school,
will it be more tiring
than undergrad?
Grad school will probably
be pretty tiring too.
(Concerned)
You'll probably spend most of your time
in the school lab?
Yeah.
So how many times
a week do you think we should meet?
Maybe three times.
(Glances)
What do you think?
Do you think that's too little?
Not really.
We're not that far apart anyway.
Yeah, it actually feels really close.
Even just
grabbing a meal together counts.
What about what we agreed on last time?
Video calls every day?
That's a must.
Depends on how busy you are too.
If you're upset, I'm not busy.
(If you're upset, I'm not busy)
If you're upset,
(You know what he means)
I'm not busy.
Look at these two going back and forth.
If you're upset, I'm not busy.
But I don't want you to feel pressured.
Even if we say we'll
video call every day,
if you're too tired one day
and don't feel like calling,
or just want to rest,
that's totally fine.
Are you the type
who calls again if they don't answer?
Definitely not.
If you don't answer, you must be busy.
Would you get mad if I didn't tell you?
Why would I get mad for no reason?
I think I'd probably
want to call every day.
Even if I'm exhausted,
after calling you,
I'd probably feel better.
Because sometimes
I get pretty stressed,
and I need someone to support me.
Got it.
How would you support someone?
First, I'd try
to put myself in your shoes.
I'd think about what
you did that day
and what you need most.
But most importantly,
don't go hungry.
(Don't go hungry)
Then we can send each other
good food every day.
Sure.
You're done stringing it?
(Made by Cao Yiheng)
Looks good.
(Made by Cui Kaiyi)
So pretty.
It looks so good.
Here.
Try it on.
Mine fits perfectly.
Not too loose or tight.
Quick.
Next one.
Let's just make two.
Do you ever feel like
the Signal House is kind of
a dreamy place?
Like it's not real?
Like when it comes
to being together later,
is there anything
you're worried about?
Or anything like that?
Different relationship styles.
What about you?
I'm just worried
because I'm a little oblivious.
Like,
sometimes I feel like
I might miss how you're feeling.
Don't worry.
You're such a confident girl.
Why are you always worrying?
I only worry
when it comes to people I'm close to.
(I only worry
when it comes to people I'm close to)
Because she cares.
That's why she's scared
she'll miss something he's feeling.
(I only worry
when it comes to people I'm close to)
It's like the room
I picked at the start.
(Cui Kaiyi chose Secure Love)
Because I really want
a stable relationship.
Something dependable.
(Cao Yiheng chose Independent Love)
So I worry that
certain things I do
might secretly cost me points with you.
So I just want to say,
if something's bothering you,
just tell me.
Got it.
And don't put too much pressure
on yourself.
Sometimes,
I get upset pretty easily.
You don't have to constantly
manage my feelings.
Honestly, the sense
of security you give me
is already more than enough.
You don't have to ask me first anymore.
I'll
come tell you myself.
(I'll tell you myself)
Okay.
Our birthdays are actually pretty close.
They're both around Lunar New Year.
How does your family usually
celebrate your birthday?
If I feel like having home-cooked food,
I'll eat at home.
My dad's a pretty good cook.
Both my parents cook really well.
When we're back,
you can come over
and try it.
You can come over and try it.
(You can come over and try it)
Then he'll eat well over New Year.
Something to look forward to next year.
(Looking forward to spending next
Lunar New Year at your place)
Something to look forward to next year.
Next year, he'll eat at Cui Kaiyi's place.
They'll spend New Year together.
Something to look forward to next year.
(Looking forward to spending next
Lunar New Year at your place)
(Turns to look)
Okay.
One goes "hehehe".
The other goes "hahaha".
Here.
Doesn't this fit perfectly?
Yeah, perfect.
This is so pretty.
It kind of looks like
Shine Muscat grapes.
Done.
They've been talking nonstop,
and their hands haven't stopped either.
Right.
Not bad.
It's about as good as mine.
You've got some skills.
This is seriously so pretty.
They go really well together.
They really do.
I'll wear it every day from now on.
Me too.
Those two are just
going back and forth,
(Yiheng and Kaiyi going back and forth)
like they're playing ping-pong.
One after the other.
They've got a great rhythm.
And they're even
planning their future together.
Going back home together.
Right.
Once school starts,
how many times a week
he'll go see her...
And even going over for dinner.
Agreed.
See each other whenever you want.
They're in the honeymoon phase.
Whenever there's time,
they should just
stick together.
The good thing about them
is that
they talk things through.
Yeah.
One of them's starting school.
And you can see the guy
takes the initiative
to ask her
"Do you think three days"
"is too little?"
Is it too little?
Chaoyue,
if you were dating someone,
how often would you want to meet?
(Caught off guard by the pop quiz)
Me?
I just think that
for everyone,
once you're an adult,
work
matters a bit more.
So I think
you should meet
whenever it works comfortably
for both of you.
Right.
Cao Yiheng and Cui Kaiyi's
date isn't over yet.
So what
will happen next
on their date?
You'll get to see it
next week.
Alright, that's it
for today's episode.
This show
is presented by Master Kong
Sugar-Free Jasmine Tea.
Freshly scented for 24 hours.
Every sip is as fragrant
as the first blossom.
Every Thursday at 12PM,
don't miss the bonus episode,
featuring even more
heart-fluttering moments.
Every Friday at 12PM,
catch the companion program,
"Watching Heart Signal with You",
for even more exclusive content.
Visit WeTV Grassland Hub
to discover the guests'
featured merchandise
and matching collectibles.
Next week is going to be amazing!
See you next week!
(Next episode)
Feels like we're fleeing the apocalypse.
Like we're eloping.
What do you want to do right now?
Zone out.
Then let's zone out.
No closing your eyes.
I can't even close them?
(Holds on)
I'm probably not great
at expressing myself.
(Fang's observation notes)
I just wrote this.
Be yourself without holding back.
I'll take it from here.
Like tropical fruit in Hawaii...
Bursting into bloom.
Rock, paper, scissors.
You go.
Who's going upstairs first?
All these different kinds of love
are so fun to watch.
These two, every day...
You seem pretty happy every day.
Zhao Xilun's great.
That night when you left,
you looked so cool.
I even called after you.
I said, "Yue'er."
I wanted to say,
"Can you close the door for me?"
That's what you wanted to say?
What?
Why are you so happy?
I'm reading Xing's letter.
Somewhere in the house,
someone's quietly thinking of you.
So much love in so few words.
I cried my makeup off.
You still look great.
"Love-hate relationship".
What comes around will come.
My luck changes today.
Just wait.
Two people used
their Master Kong Jasmine Coins.
City date.
Stargazing room.
(Stargazing room and city date opened)
They both opened at once.
What?
Every day, you have no idea
what'll happen tomorrow.
(Who opened the city date
and stargazing room?)
(Members' early access preview)
Does making one today
feel different from before?
Of course it's different with you.
What are you looking at?
(Stares)
You look good.
Smells so good.
This feels pretty blissful.
It really does.
(Smiles)
("Watching Heart Signal with You" preview)
Welcome, Xing.
Good to see you again.
I had a follow-up yesterday.
The doctor said I'm
recovering really well.
That's great.
Everyone should remember to eat on time.
Then you'll be able
to go on dates.
Mutual-choice date.
That was the bravest I've
ever been on a date.
You liked him at that moment.
I should've been more certain.
He just wouldn't invite me,
so I told him to.
You were hoping he'd
give you his card, right?
(Confidential)
I thought he...
(Heart Signal (China Version) S9,
Viewing Calendar)
"♪Morning steam rises
from breakfast stalls♪
♪Packed subway cars,
barely room to breathe♪
♪Still half asleep, another day begins♪
♪The city glows beneath the towers♪
♪Somewhere beyond the clouds,
a sweet little date awaits♪
♪But first,
there are endless meetings to survive♪
♪Even if the fairy tale
only lasts a day♪
♪I'll still give it everything I have♪
♪Love out loud♪
♪Don't let this summer slip away♪
♪Cupid's arrow is already on its way♪
♪Don't act like you didn't see it♪
♪Just be a little braver♪
♪Keep moving♪
♪There's a little spark shining
in your eyes♪
♪That's the signal
of a heart coming alive♪
♪Keep moving♪
♪Life can be complicated,
yet beautifully simple♪
♪Go discover♪
♪That heartbeat you've been longing
to let out♪
♪Come closer♪